

Kuala Lumpur +60 19-779 9074 aisyahhanifiah@live.com

PROFILE

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Name: Nur Aisyah binti Mohd Hanifiah Date of Birth: 16 April 1996 I find joy in creating visuals that are able to engage with people effectively while fulfilling the aesthetics of each graphic element. Based on my past experiences being a graphic designer, I learnt a lot about how each graphics and type could influence the viewers. It is that everywhere I go I would think to myself on how people could improve their marketing materials. I also do work well both as a member of a team and in isolation with high attention to detail.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Amber & Sparkles | Sept 2016 - Dec 2016

- Creating graphics based on tasks given and meeting deadlines
- Developed a strong attention to details towards each task.

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

The Pixel Things | August 2016 - current

- Founder of The Pixel Things (Instagram: @thepixelthings)
- Manage projects, customers and meeting deadlines

INDUSTRIAL TRAINING

Motive Interactive Sdn, Bhd. | Feb 2017 - Jun 2017

- Assist in software development cycles for ongoing projects.
- Developed personal project using Laravel PHP frameworkhttp://leave-management-system.motive.com.my/dashboard

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Universiti Kuala Lumpur (MIIT) | June 2014 - June 2017 CGPA: 3.97

SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA

Sekolah Tun Fatimah | 2012 - 2013

Pure science

Grade: 5A+ 4A

PENILAIAN MENENGAH RENDAH

Sekolah Tun Fatimah | 2009-2011

Grade: 8A

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator PHP HTML & CSS WordPress Bootstrap MVSOL

KNOWLEDGE

JAVA
C#
C++
VB.NET
ASP.NET

PERSONAL SKILLS

TEAMWORK
CREATIVITY
ORGANIZATION
COMMUNICATION
INDEPENDENT

REFERENCES

Disclosed private information.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Malay

English